Bisma Aleem

Karachi Division, Sindh, Pakistan

CONTACT:03352110402

bismaaleem03@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/bisma-aleem-

331474266

Summary

Currently pursuing bachelor's in Computer Systems engineering. I have completed developing website using custom CSS, Bootstrap, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, Php and also with the Wordpress.

Through this platform ,I am looking forward to gain more expertise in web-development and astonishing projects with the collobration of my customers.

Experience



Oracle Database Intern

Afroze Textiles Industries Pvt. Ltd. Mar 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month) Oracle SQL Developer



Frontend Developer

Interns Pakistan

Mar 2023 - Apr 2023 (2 months)

The responsive Web Designing Using html,css,css3Flex,bootstrap,javascript,jquery,php and the final project of online ordering food website using Wordpress



NLP Intern

NCL - NED

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023 (2 months)

Worked on data pre-processing for "URDU OCR" project in which weh have extracted data from scan pdf and converted it from unstructured to structured data to improve efficiency of our model using Document AI platform for data minig task and further format that document using MS-WORD

Education



NED University of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Systems Engineering 2020 - 2024

BAMM PECHS COLLEGE

INTERMEDIATE, Pre-Engineering Apr 2018 - Apr 2020

Usman Public School System

Licenses & Certifications

- Spython Core Sololearn
- Spython For Beginners Sololearn
- Sololearn Coding For Marketers Sololearn
- S Java Sololearn
- SQI Sololearn
- 5 HTML Sololearn
- Learn DevOps for Web Development DevTown
- **↑** Data Integration Bootcamp Astera Careers
- NLP NCL NED
- Outstanding Performance Award Hamdard Foundation Pakistan
- Academic Excellence Award Usman Public School System
- Future Of Technology IEEE GCU Student Branch
- Basic of HTML,CSS Training Open Weaver

Skills

Front-End Development • Adobe Illustrator • Video Production • Video Editing • Microsoft Office • Project Management • Natural Language Processing (NLP) • Oracle SQL Developer • Python (Programming Language) • Canva